YICHI ZHANG

+1(734)800-6032 \(\phi\) yichiz@umich.edu \(\phi\) Website: https://yichiz97.github.io/
4352 North Quad, 510 State St., Ann Arbor, MI 48109, U.S.A.

RESEARCH INTERESTS

Ph.D. candidate with research focuses on the intersection between computer science and economics, in particular, information elicitation and aggregation, mechanism design and their interactions with machine learning. Comfortable in using programming and mathematical tools to solve multi-agent problems including crowdsourcing, peer grading, peer reviewing, and recommender systems. Experienced with big data analysis and causal analysis.

EDUCATION

University of Michigan, Ann Arbor (Umich)

Sep 2019 - Present

- Ph.D. in School of Information
- Advisor: Grant Schoenebeck
- Thesis: Incentive Design for Data-driven Systems: Effort and Information Elicitation

Shanghai Jiao Tong University (SJTU)

Aug 2015 - Jun 2019

- B.S. in Electronic Science and Engineering
- Advisor: Xinbing Wang and Luoyi Fu

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Sep 2019 - Present

Research Assistant, Useful Theory Innovation Lab

UCLA, Department of Computer Science

Jul 2018 - Sep 2018

Research Intern (The CSST program), working with Mario Gerla

YITUTech Algorithm Engineer Intern

Feb 2019 - May 2019

SUBMISSIONS UNDER REVIEW

Understanding When Peer Grades (Definitely) Outperform Instructor Grades Noah Burrell, Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

PUBLICATIONS

Spot Check Equivalence: an Interpretable Metric for Information Elicitation Mechanisms Shengwei Xu, Yichi Zhang, Paul Resnick and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 33nd Annual World Wide Web Conference

(WWW 2024)

Eliciting Honest Information From Authors Using Sequential Review

Yichi Zhang, Grant Schoenebeck and Weijie Su

In Proceedings of the 38th Annual AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI 2024)
[https://arxiv.org/abs/2311.14619]

Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 32nd Annual World Wide Web Conference (WWW 2023)
[https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3543507.3583292]

High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

Yichi Zhang and Grant Schoenebeck

In Proceedings of the 32nd Annual World Wide Web Conference (WWW 2023)
[https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3543507.3583334]

A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

Yichi Zhang, Fang-Yi Yu, Grant Schoenebeck and David Kempe In Proceedings of the 23rd ACM Conference on Economics and Computation [https://arxiv.org/abs/2303.09020]

 $(EC \ 2022)$

Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

Grant Schoenebeck, Fang-Yi Yu and **Yichi Zhang** (ranked by alphabet) In Proceedings of the 30th Annual World Wide Web Conference [https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3442381.3449840]

(WWW 2021)

POSTERS

Eliciting Effort And Truth-telling From Parties of (No) Interest

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2023)

Multi-task Peer Prediction Under Task-Dependent Strategies

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2023)

A System-Level Analysis of Conference Peer Review

- ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2022)
- U-M Asian American Faculty & Student Accomplishments Symposium (2022)

High-Effort Crowds: Limited Liability Via Tournaments

• ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2022)

Information Elicitation From Rowdy Crowds

- DIMACS Workshop on Forecasting (2021)
- ACM Conference on Economics and Computation (2021)

SELECTED TALKS

Improving Conference Review Via Mechanism Design

• Renmin University of China, Gaoling School of Artificial Intelligence

August 2023

• Peking University, CFCS seminar

July 2023

University of Michigan, DSCSS seminar
 University of Pennsylvania, Wharton Statistics and Data Science
 March 2023

Eliciting Honest Information From Authors Using Sequential Review

• Harvard University, EconCS seminar

January 2024

TEACHING

Teaching assistant (GSI), Umich

Winter 2022

Courses: Big Data Analysis (SI 699)
Instructor: Misha Teplitskiy

Teaching assistant (GSI), Umich

Fall 2021

Course: Deep Learning (SIADS 642) Instructor: Paramveer Dhillon

Course: Network Analysis (SIADS 642)

Instructor: Daniel Romero

AWARDS

• The Web Conference Student Scholarship.	2021
• Nominee for the Rackham International Student Fellowship, UMSI.	2021
• Outstanding Graduate of Shanghai Jiao Tong University.	2019
• EIC Education Scholarship (top 5%).	2018
• Samsung Scholarship (top 3%).	2017

SERVICE

Reviewer/PC member:

• The Web Conference (WWW): 2024, 2023, 2022

• Economics and Computation (EC): 2023, 2022

• Web and Internet Economics (WINE): 2023

Workflow Volunteer: EC 2024